[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does Jack suspect about Greg in the 2004 comedy movie Meet the Fockers?", "correct_answer": "That he has a son", "incorrect_answers": ["That he does drugs", "That he is gay", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film Point Break, during a stake out, agent Pappas orders Utah to get some take out food. What does he want him to get?", "correct_answer": "Meatball sub", "incorrect_answers": ["Hamburger, all the way", "Meat loaf", "Meat lovers pizza"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In motion picture, Pulp Fiction, what country is the taxi driver, Esmerelda Villalobos, from?", "correct_answer": "Colombia", "incorrect_answers": ["Spain", "Mexico", "Venezuela"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Crop circles, the cause of many contending believes, were adapted by a creative Swedish company for this rather rational purpose.", "correct_answer": "Advertisement", "incorrect_answers": ["Crop fertilization", "Conceptual modern art", "Airplane navigation"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Walnuts contain only unsaturated fats and therefore decrease the risk of heart disease.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The real McCoy refers to the man who invented this.", "correct_answer": "The locomotive self-lubricator", "incorrect_answers": ["The train throttle", "The sewing machine", "The train coupling"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Unfortunately this fictional dog is constantly bullied by his buddy cat.", "correct_answer": "Odie", "incorrect_answers": ["Snoopy", "Lucky", "Goofy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This flowering plant, native to the eastern Mediterranean region and southwest Asia, is used as a spice in different liqueurs like raki and ouzo.", "correct_answer": "Anise", "incorrect_answers": ["Chicory", "Cardamon", "Allspice"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The largest penguin species on the planet is the Emperor Penguin. What is the smallest one?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Blue Penguin", "Little Penguin", "Fairy Penguin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In order to preserve their elaborate coiffures, these women slept with their heads on bags filled with buckwheat chaff.", "correct_answer": "Geishas in Japan", "incorrect_answers": ["Oracles in Africa", "Queens in Britain", "First Ladies in the US"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What best describes the climate of Eilat?", "correct_answer": "Hot and dry all year", "incorrect_answers": ["Humid and hot  summers and humid and cool winters", "Humid, hot summers and dry, cool winters", "Hot, dry summers and humid, cool winters"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How did Jane Seymour, wife of King Henry VIII of England, die in 1537?", "correct_answer": "Of natural causes", "incorrect_answers": ["She was executed.", "She committed suicide.", "She was poisoned."]}]